
export const quizQuestions_8 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is JSX in the context of ReactJS?',
      choices: ['A JavaScript extension for XML', 'A special syntax for writing components in React', 'A library for handling asynchronous operations in React', 'A tool for optimizing React components'],
      correctAnswer: 'A special syntax for writing components in React',
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you render a React component within another component?',
      choices: ['<Component />', 'renderComponent(Component)', '{Component}', 'render(Component)'],
      correctAnswer: '<Component />',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the props object in a React component?',
      choices: ['To manage state within the component', 'To define default values for the component', 'To pass data from a parent component to a child component', 'To handle lifecycle events'],
      correctAnswer: 'To pass data from a parent component to a child component',
    },
    {
      question: 'In JSX, how do you interpolate a JavaScript expression?',
      choices: ['{ expression }', '[ expression ]', '( expression )', '{{ expression }}'],
      correctAnswer: '{ expression }',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the significance of the key attribute in React elements?',
      choices: ['To define a unique identifier for an element', 'To specify the order of elements in the component', 'To set default values for props', 'To handle conditional rendering'],
      correctAnswer: 'To define a unique identifier for an element',
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you apply inline styles to a React element in JSX?',
      choices: ['style={styles}', 'styles={styles}', 'css={styles}', 'applyStyle={styles}'],
      correctAnswer: 'style={styles}',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the className attribute in React components?',
      choices: ['To define a class in JavaScript', 'To add inline styles to a component', 'To specify the class of an HTML element', 'To set the unique identifier of a component'],
      correctAnswer: 'To specify the class of an HTML element',
    },
    {
      question: 'In React, what is the significance of the curly braces {} in JSX?',
      choices: ['To denote an object literal', 'To create a JavaScript block within JSX', 'To define a string literal', 'To indicate a self-closing tag'],
      correctAnswer: 'To create a JavaScript block within JSX',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can you conditionally render content in a React component based on a variable?',
      choices: ['Using the if statement', 'By directly placing the variable in JSX', 'Using the switch statement', 'Using the ternary operator'],
      correctAnswer: 'Using the ternary operator',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the useState hook in functional components?',
      choices: ['To handle asynchronous operations', 'To define state in functional components', 'To connect components to the Redux store', 'To perform side effects in functional components'],
      correctAnswer: 'To define state in functional components',
    },
  ],
}